A Guide to the Records of the Choices and Challenges Forum, ca. 1985-2003
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series IV. Audiocassette Tapes, 1985-1989
  - Forum 5: New Coal Mining and Combustion Technologies, 1986 (Box 9)
    Talks by Michael Quillen and Curtis Seltzer; Talks by Helen Lewis and James Zoia; Panel discussion; Discussion Group: Extended Ecosystem; Discussion Group: Workplace Environment; Discussion Group: Coal and the Local Community
  - Forum 7: Genetic Engineering, 1986 (Box 9)
    Discussion at AAUW program held on November 24, 1986
  - Forum 12: Pesticide Dilemma, 1989 (Box 9)
    Discussion Group: Alternatives to Agricultural Pesticides
  - Forum 15: Quality of Life at the End of Life, 1994
    - The Hospice Option, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Ethical Perspectives, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Religious Perspectives, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Rubric Policy Options, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Quality of Life at the End of Life - Legal Perspectives - Greg Campbell, 1994-03 (Box 15)
  - Forum 16: Quality of Life in the Electronic Village, 1995
    - Technology Tutorial - Scott Midkiff, 1995-03-30 (Box 14)
    - The Status of Social Interchange - Ellsworth Fuhrman, 1995 (Box 14)
    - On-Line Legal Documents - Sharic Steele (EFF), 1995 (Box 14)
    - Case Study: The Telephone, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Encouraging New Voices - Barbara Rugs and Lawrence Lumdblade, 1995 (Box 14)
    - On-line Legal Dilemmas - Sharic Steele (EFF), 1995 (Box 14)
    - Living In and With Cybersapce - Len Natfield, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Sociological Perspective - William Snizek, 1995-03-30 (Box 14)
    - Community Networking (BEV) - Andrea Karanaugh, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Philosophy Tutorial - John Christman and Garry Hardcastle, 1995-03-30 (Box 14)
    - Lake Gaston Pipeline Controversy - William Cox, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Artistic Creativity and Computer Networks - Panel Discussion (Music and Visual Arts), 1995-03-30 (Box 15)
  - Forum 17: Sharing the Earth's Water Supply, 1996
    - Learning About Water - A Tutorial - David Kibler, 1996
    - Sessions for Saving VAs Water - Lake Gaston Controversy Tape 1, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Literature and Ecology - Len Scigaj, 1996 (Box 14)
    - New/Old Approaches to Religion and Ecology - Elizabeth Bounds, 1997 (Box 14)
    - Religious Traditions and the Environment - Elizabeth Bounds, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Cross-cultural Views of Nature Panel Discussion, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Rise of American Environmentalism - Mark V. Barrow, Jr., 1996 (Box 15)
    - Water and Government Policy - John Randolph, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Ethical Issues in Water Use - Pat Croskery and Harlam Miller, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Sessions for Saving VAs Water - Lake Gaston Controversy Tape 2, 1196 (Box 14)
  - Forum 18: Preparing for the Next Century, 1997
    - Women in the Developing World - Mary Hill Rojas, 1997 (Box 13)
    - Human/Environmental Interactions: A Snapshot - David Conn, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Global Economic Equity Issues - John Browder, 1997 (Box 14)
    - Sustainable Urban Development - Rick Roth, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Environmental Ethics - P. Croskery and H. Miller, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Environmental Politics - Tim Luke, 1997-04-03 (Box 15)
    - Economics Tutorial - Jeff Alwang, 1997 (Box 15)
  - Various Tapes
    - Cross Cultural Views, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Legal Perspectives, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Sociological Perspectives, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Ethical Perspectives (Box 14)
    - Internet etc., 1995-05-12 (Box 15)
    - Choices and Challenges Teleconference, 1994-03-24 (Box 15)
    - Choices and Challenges 95' Part 2, 1995 (Box 15)
    - WVTF Evening Edition - Show on Big Brother Technologies, 2003-03-25 (Box 15)
    - Unnamed Tape Part 1 - Side 1 (Box 16)
    - Unnamed Tape Part 2 Side 1 (Box 15)
    - Unnamed Tape (Box 15)
    - Unnamed Tape (Box 15)
    - Unnamed Tape Reel 1 - S-A and S-B (Box 16)
- Series V. CDs, 1992-2001
  - Various Unnamed CDs (Box 16)
  - Choices Website, 2001-12-07 (Box 13)
  - Website Back-up (Box 13)
  - Broker (Box 13)
  - Choices and Challenges CD, 1992-1997, 1999-2000, 2002 (Box 13)
- Series VI. Floppy Disks, 1992-2003
  - Various Disks (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges VA - 9530875, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges - Health Care Related - 9530879, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges Back-up Files 1 of 2, 2000-08-04 (Box 16)
    - Page Maker Files Choices and Challenges - Jane Lehr (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges Back-up Files 2 of 2, 2000-08-04 (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges Big Brother Technology, 2003-03-12 (Box 16)
      Posters, Brochures, Eudora Speakers
    - Choices and Challenges, 2002-01 (Box 16)
    - Eudora Back-up Folder (from System Folder), 2003-04-23 (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges Transcripts, 1992-1997 (Box 16)
    - Unnamed (Box 16)
    - Unnamed (Box 16)
    - Unnamed (Box 16)
  - 1994 (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges, 1994-12-20 (Box 16)
      Brochure 3/24/1994
    - CHD 1 Choices and Challenges, 1994 (Box 16)
      Choices and Challenges info, Video/TV, Outreach, NEH 94-95
    - CHD 2 Choices and Challenges, 1994 (Box 16)
      Contacts, labels, letters - 94
    - CHD 3 Choices and Challenges, 1994 (Box 16)
      Pub - 94, 94 Evals, 94-Thanks, Outreach, NEH 94-95 Final Report
    - Choices and Challenges 94 and 95, 1994-1995 (Box 16)
      Brochurs for 1 pg, flyer (grants, etc.)
    - CHD - Choices and Challenges, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges (4), 1994 (Box 16)
      94 Transcript and mail labels, 94 Open Univeristy program, 1992 - HGP
    - 1994 (1) Back-up, 1994 (Box 16)
    - 1994 (2) Back-up, 1994 (Box 16)
    - 1994 (3) Back-up, 1994 (Box 16)
    - 1994 Choices and Challenges (4), 1994 (Box 16)
  - 1995 (Box 16)
    - 1995 Choices and Challenges Transcript, 1995 (Box 16)
    - 95 Transcript (MW), 1995 (Box 16)
      Labels, marketing letters, etc.
    - Unnamed (Box 16)
    - 1995 - Pagemaker, 1995 (Box 16)
      Display, lunch invitation, registration, ads, brochure
    - Email (1995), 1995 (Box 16)
    - 1995 Choices and Challenges (Box 16)
      Program Development, DZ addresses, Timeline, NEH 94-95 Final Report
    - Printing Services Lisa, 1995 (Box 16)
      95 Brochure Final
    - Fall 1997 - Summer 1998: In the Classroom, In the Community, Activities Report, 1997-1998 (Box 16)
    - Fonts/Sounds (Box 16)
    - Day of Forum (Box 16)
    - Logos - Choices and Challenges, VT, VFH (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges Web (Box 16)
    - 95 Pagemaker (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges Web (Box 16)
    - Letters and Community Programs, 1995 (Box 16)
    - Evals, Timeline, Community Programs, 1995 (Box 16)
    - Letters and Publicity, 1995 (Box 16)
    - Transcript - Pagemaker, 1995 (Box 16)
    - 1995 Transcript, 1995 (Box 16)
      95 Transcript - Microsoft Word, Labels, Special Requests, Marketing Labels
    - 1995 Choices and Challenges, 1995 (Box 16)
      Program Development, 95 Contracts, 95 Pub, Lavels (94+), 95 Evals
    - Transcriptions, DT Interviews, QOL Transcript, 1995 (Box 16)
    - DTL - CV Interviews (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges (Box 16)
    - ZIP Sort.xls from Ag Econ (Box 16)
    - For Chris - Poster (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges Bib (Box 16)
  - 1996 (Box 16)
    - Unnamed (Box 16)
    - Unnamed (Box 16)
    - Unnamed (Box 16)
    - Choices and Challenges - 96 Transcript Microsoft Word, 1996 (Box 16)
    - 1996 Transcript and Transcript Requests, 1996 (Box 16)
      Includes bib
    - 1996 Forum Brochure and Community Programs, 1996 (Box 16)
    - 1996 Publicity A, 1996 (Box 16)
      Early notices, Press Releases, Display Ads, CEC Mail List
    - 1996 Publicity B, 1996 (Box 16)
      Lavels, Posters/Flyers
    - 1996 Forum, 1996 (Box 16)
      Intro/Case Studies - Water, Outlines of Forum Sessions, Evals
    - 1996 PBS, NEH, VFH, 1996 (Box 16)
    - 1996 Quality of Life...Global Environment - Part I, 1996 (Box 16)
  - 1997 (Box 16)
    - Letters and Labels, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Forum Info - PBS, NEH, VFH, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Publicity C, 1997 (Box 16)
      Transcript requests and order forms, 97 Graphics
    - Publicity A - Brochure (Box 16)
      Press releases, display ad letters, CEC mail list requests, pub. cover letters
    - Publicity B and Evals, 1997 (Box 16)
      Poster, BT Poster
    - Publicity D - Display Ads, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Transcript (with Bib), 1997 (Box 16)
    - Brochure Back-up 2, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Community Programs, 1996-1997 (Box 16)
    - House/Senate/Congress - Slides from Press Office, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Transcripts, 1996-1997 (Box 16)
  - 1999 (Box 16)
    - Label Files in Excel, 1999 (Box 16)
      Attn: Science Dept Labels; Attn: Social Studies Dept; Principals of Alt. Schools; CEC Labels; Kirsten Worley
    - Poster and Pagemaker 6.0, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Genetics 99 Poster Pagemaker, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Forum Designer Children Website Files, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Brochure Pagemaker 6.0 Baby/DNA Image Tiff File, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Brochure Draft with Graphics, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Brochure, 1999 (Box 16)
    - 1999, 1999 (Box 16)
- Series VII. Posters, 1985-2003
  - Forum posters, 1985-2003 (Box 10)
  - The Choices and Challenges Project - exploring the social and ethical dimensions of science and technology, presentation poster about the project, ca. 2001 (Box 11)
- Series VIII. Teleconference Transcripts, 1992-1997
  - The Human Genome Project, 1992-04-09 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Quality of Life at the End of Life, 1994-03-24 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Quality of Life in the Electronic Village, 1995-03-30 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Quality of Life in the Global Environment: Preparing for the Next Century, 1997-04-03 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Quality of Life in the Global Environment: Sharing the Earth's Water Supply, 1996-10-17 (Box 17, Folder 5)